<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog.atom"/>
  <title>Better Baby Boutique - Better Baby Fashion Blog</title>
  <updated>2020-11-25T01:27:04-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Better Baby Boutique</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog/better-babys-ceo-ariselis-offers-expert-advice-on-redfin</id>
    <published>2020-11-25T01:27:04-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-25T01:28:25-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog/better-babys-ceo-ariselis-offers-expert-advice-on-redfin"/>
    <title>Better Baby&apos;s CEO, Ariselis, Offers Expert Advice On REDFIN</title>
    <author>
      <name>Michael Siciliano</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>Looking for simple ways to keep your child’s room organized, let’s start with the less is more. Fill your child’s room with toys that are interactive so they don’t need more...</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog/better-babys-ceo-ariselis-offers-expert-advice-on-redfin">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Recently our CEO, Ariselis Siciliano, was approached by a representative at REDFIN to offer advice on the following topic:11 Tips for Organizing Your Entire House. Check out what Ariselis had to say and get some expert kid's room organization advice right now!</p>
<p><a href="https://www.redfin.com/blog/tips-for-organizing-your-entire-house/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://www.redfin.com/blog/tips-for-organizing-your-entire-house/</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog/why-shopping-for-baby-clothes-online-will-save-you-time-money</id>
    <published>2019-08-26T10:20:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-08-26T10:26:23-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog/why-shopping-for-baby-clothes-online-will-save-you-time-money"/>
    <title>Why Shopping For Baby Clothes Online Will Save You Time &amp; Money</title>
    <author>
      <name>Ariselis Siciliano</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span><span>Save yourself time &amp; money right now by shopping for baby clothes online with us or any other vendor for that matter. Leverage the convenience of your mobile device and start browsing for your baby’s necessities today, and then take a nap because you deserve it. </span></span><meta charset="utf-8"><span>Between the stress of unstable income and raging post pregnancy hormones, I found myself grasping the reality around me for more time, and more importantly, more sleep. When the baby went down for a nap, of course my insomnia had to show itself in the most prominent of ways, so I tried to curb that by browsing through social media, and what I found was astonishing.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog/why-shopping-for-baby-clothes-online-will-save-you-time-money">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2587/9172/files/better-baby-dresses-pinterest_grande.png?v=1566829481" alt="Online Baby Clothes"></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Two and a half years ago when I gave birth to the love of my life I was awakened to a pain point that millions of Americans in my shoes also felt. Without the help of family and a husband with a new job, and trying to kick-start my baby clothing company, keeping up with my mini’s needs took a toll on me both physically and mentally. Between the stress of unstable income and raging post pregnancy hormones, I found myself grasping the reality around me for more time, and more importantly, more sleep. When the baby went down for a nap, of course my insomnia had to show itself in the most prominent of ways, so I tried to curb that by browsing through social media, and what I found was astonishing. There were hundreds of other online shops just like mine selling baby clothes, baby accessories, baby necessities, and much more. Because I designed our baby clothes and took pride in my business, I only purchased baby clothes from my own store, Better Baby Boutique, BUT I did shop for bibs, bows, swaddles, bottles, and so much more online only. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Problem With Retail Shopping</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The luxury of shopping online comes down to convenience for new moms. As a new mom, getting yourself and your baby ready is an evolution with fast changing variables that can drive your mission off course on a moment’s notice from dirty diapers, to milk spills, and so much more. After 20 mins of negotiating your departure with your mini, you drive, park, load mini into a stroller and start navigating your way through the store. Finally, you reach the baby clothing aisle only to be interrupted by your crying bundle of joy who needs another diaper change. After completing the changing mission in a cramped, uncleanly public restroom, you make your way back to the aisle to finish shopping. Repeat this process 2 more times and you’ll finally make your way to the checkout line. From there, you begin navigating your phone for any and all available coupons only to see the fine print reads “*FOR ONLINE USE ONLY”. After overpaying 20 dollars, and navigating yourself through rush hour traffic, you find yourself back at the house. While placing the clothes on hangers and into the closet, you notice that you already have the ever-so-common Mini Mouse onesie given to you by Aunt Jenny at the baby shower and another trip instantly presents itself with the final destination being the return/exchange line. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Simplicity of Online Shopping</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">How can shopping for <a href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/collections/baby-girl-rompers" title="Baby Rompers">Baby Rompers</a>, <a href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/collections/baby-dresses" title="Baby Dresses">Baby Dresses</a>, <a href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/collections/baby-girl-outfits" title="Baby Outfits">Baby Outfits</a> and more online combat the nightmare on retail street? For starters, you won’t waste time or gas during the commute to and from the store BOTH times for the initial purchase and the return. You can navigate to your baby’s closet if you are willing to take a 20-step trip down the hall to check what items are already present in his/her wardrobe. There are hundreds of coupons available not only for Better Baby Boutique, but most other online retailers, so you know you’re getting the best possible price for your selections. Shopping can commence during your mini’s nap, interruption free. On Better Baby Boutique, all items are sure to turn heads and they are delivered within 2-5 days from ordering. Because our online baby clothing store is family owned and operated, we take pride in your order, so all items are hand-inspected for quality assurance and you have the option to exchange by mail should they not fit. </span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">So what are you waiting for? Save yourself time &amp; money right now by shopping for baby clothes online with us or any other vendor. Leverage the convenience of your mobile device and start browsing for your baby’s necessities today, and then take a nap because you deserve it. </span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog/the-hottest-fall-2019-baby-fashion-trends</id>
    <published>2019-08-12T16:43:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-08-14T13:16:37-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog/the-hottest-fall-2019-baby-fashion-trends"/>
    <title>The Hottest Fall 2019 Baby Fashion Trends</title>
    <author>
      <name>Ariselis Siciliano</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>Fall is just about here and it’s time to Better your Baby! We’re so excited for fall to arrive and expect this season’s baby clothing patterns, styles, &amp; trends to melt hearts everywhere. So without any further ado let’s dive into the hottest Baby Fashion of Fall 2019.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/blogs/better-baby-fashion-blog/the-hottest-fall-2019-baby-fashion-trends">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2587/9172/files/fall-2019-baby-fashion_large.jpg?v=1565802987" alt=""></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fall is just about here and it’s time to Better your Baby! We’re so excited for fall to arrive and expect this season’s baby clothing patterns, styles, &amp; trends to melt hearts everywhere. So without any further ado let’s dive into the hottest Baby Fashion of Fall 2019.</span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Baby Jumpsuits</span></h2>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2587/9172/products/wide-knot-baby-jumpsuit-garnet_large.jpg?v=1565303657" alt=""></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Did somebody say jumpsuits? Well they should have! Baby Jumpsuits are at the top of our list for the cutest baby fall fashion items. Frilled sleeves, stripped, or wide-bottom baby jumpsuits are sure to turn heads towards your little mini as other moms watch your beautiful clone strut passed with all of her jumpsuit sass. We hate to keep it basic, but it’s another earth toned fall headed your way - we don’t make the rules, we just enforce them.</span></p>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/collections/baby-girl-rompers" target="_blank" title="Baby Girl Rompers &amp; Jumpsuits" rel="noopener noreferrer">Shop Baby Rompers &amp; Jumpsuits &gt;</a></strong></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ribbed Baby Clothes</span></h2>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2587/9172/products/s905524150898975867_p325_i6_w768_large.jpg?v=1562722474" alt=""></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Ribbed everything. Yes that’s right, ribbed leggings, dresses, tunics and more is our fashion-forward agenda this fall. Both comfortable and stylish, ribbed baby clothing styles are the perfect way to keep your baby warm and stylish. Form-fitting ribbed baby leggings are a comfortable alternative to thick, heavy jeans and can be found in a wide variety of colors, shapes, and sizes throughout our website. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Knee-High Socks</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2587/9172/files/knee-high-baby-socks_large.jpg?v=1565728545" alt="Knee High Baby Socks"></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It wouldn’t be fall without a few dozen pairs of knee-high baby socks in our favorite earth tones or spiced up plaids. Knee-high baby socks pair perfectly with baby tunics, <a href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/collections/baby-dresses" title="Baby Dresses">Baby Dresses</a>, <a href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/collections/baby-girl-rompers" title="Baby Girl Rompers">Baby Rompers</a> and so much more. Fill up her warm bottle of pumpkin spiced milk and hit the playground knee-high as all of the other baby’s post up on the sideline in admiration of your sunshine’s style and dare to flair. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dresses With Tights</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2587/9172/products/dress-up-buttercup-baby-girl-dress_large.jpg?v=1565458270" alt=""></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">After polling our mommas through social media, dresses paired with tights are going to be a hit this Fall and Fall-diggity you’re in luck - shop a wide assortment of <a href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/collections/baby-dresses" title="Baby Dresses">Baby Dresses</a> &amp; tights on our website for the perfect Fall ready combo to keep her dressed to impress. Again, earth tones and plaid styles are up for grabs throughout our store. Whether she’s at daycare or supper, everyone will love her.</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong><a href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/collections/baby-dresses" target="_blank" title="Baby Dresses" rel="noopener noreferrer">Shop Baby Dresses &gt;</a></strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Have you heard of Better Baby Boutique yet? Shop stylish and affordable baby clothes all-year-round from our online store. Fast shipping and excellent customer services make for the perfect shopping experience. Family owned and operated out of Orlando, FL, we care about our customers and constantly evolve our business to better fit their needs. Shop our <a href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/collections/new" title="New Releases">New Release</a> collection for daily additions, or get lucky in our <a href="https://www.betterbabyboutique.com/collections/clearance" title="Clearance">Clearance</a> collection for even lower prices. Have questions, contact us through our website or <a href="https://www.instagram.com/better_baby_boutique/" target="_blank" title="Better Baby Instagram Account" rel="noopener noreferrer">Instagram</a>. Don’t forget to tag us for the chance to be featured on our social media platforms!</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
